ilovetoreview.com 2019-03-09

# Privacy policy - iLoveToReview

Privacy policy

Welcome to iLoveToReview.com. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information about you.

**1\. OUR PRIVACY COMMITMENT**

iLoveToReview.com (“ILTR”, “we,” “us” or “our”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of the iLoveToReview.com website where this Privacy Policy is posted (the “Site”) (we refer to the Site and the services made available through the Site, collectively, as “ILTR Features”. As such, we have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform visitors to the Site and users of the ILTR Features how we use and protect the information we collect through the Site and ILTR Features. By visiting the Site or using any of the ILTR Features, you consent to ILTR’s collection, use, storage, deletion and disclosure of information relating to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth above and is only applicable to the Site and not to any other website that you may be able to access from the Site which may have its own data collection and use practices and policies.

This policy answers the following questions:

1\. What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?

2\. Will we share your personal information with third parties?

3\. What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?

4\. What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

**1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND HOW DO WE USE IT?**

**Types of Information We Collect**

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you. You need to submit personal information to access certain aspects of the Site and the ILTR Features.  
We collect personal information when you subscribe to our newsletter; participate in feedback forms, questionnaires, contests or sweepstakes; purchase a product through the ILTR Features; or receive customer or technical support.

We collect information from you such as your name, address, email address, telephone number and date of birth when utilizing the Site and ILTR Features. When registering products through the Site we also collect information about your products and where you purchased your products.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

The personal information you provide to us will allow us to fulfill any product or service orders; alert you of new products or services, features, or enhancements; handle your customer service questions or issues; administer promotions, contests and sweepstakes; and notify you of promotions, updates, or special offers that we think may interest you. We also use your email address and phone number as part of the ILTR  Features in sending you messages about the ILTR  Features and other general announcements.

We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your activity within the ILTR  Features. We may use personal information that you provide to us to send messages to you in response to your request to perform an activity in connection with your use of any of the ILTR  Features. We may also use your personal information to contact you when necessary.

We may use your personal information with non-personal information that we have collected in a manner such that the end-product does not personally identify you or any other user of the ILTR  Features. We may make your personal information non-personally identifiable by either combining it with information about other users (aggregating your personal information with information about other users), or by removing characteristics (such as your name or email address) that make the information personally identifiable. This process is known as de-personalizing your information.

You grant us a royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable and fully transferable right and license to use your personal information in connection with the creation and development of analytical and statistical analysis tools relating to the use of the customer data we collect in providing the ILTR  Features (the Analytical Data). We are expressly authorized to make any commercial use of the Analytical Data, including without limitation, sharing the Analytical Data with third parties, provided that we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer from us any part of the Analytical Data that personally identifies any ILTR  Features users.

**Cookies**

“Cookies” are small bits of electronic information that a website sends to a visitor’s browser and are stored on the visitor’s hard drive. Like many websites, we employ cookies in certain areas of the Site to allow us to provide information to make your online experience more convenient. For example, when you return to the Site after logging in, cookies provide information to the Site so that the Site will remember who you are on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of the ILTR  Features by, for instance, tailoring content to you. Cookies also prevent items placed in a shopping basket from disappearing by the time you checkout.

**Log Information**

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit the Site. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, your browser type and version, the search engine you used to find the ILTR  Features, if any, which ILTR  Features you use and when and how long you use them. We use this information to monitor and analyze how users use the ILTR  Features, to provide customer service and to maintain and improve the ILTR  Features.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. We take children’s privacy seriously, and encourage parents to play an active role in their children’s online experience at all times.

**3\. WILL WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?**

**Sharing of Information**

We use your personal information to complete transactions, respond to your requests, deliver products and services you request, and send communications to you about promotions, updates, or special offers (which may be offered by ILTR  or one of its business partners) that may be of interest to you. We may also use your personal information to provide analyses of our users in the aggregate (including Analytical Data subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy) to prospective partners and other third parties. In addition, we will share the personal information we collect from you under the following circumstances:

**Protection of rights**

We will share personal information if we have a good faith belief that (i) access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or a request by law enforcement or governmental authorities, (ii) such action is appropriate to enforce our [Terms of Use](http://www.ilovetoreview.com/terms-of-use/)  for the ILTR  Features, including any investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) such action is necessary to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues associated with the ILTR  Features, or (iv) such action is appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of ILTR, its employees, users of the ILTR  Features or others.

**Asset transfers**

If we become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of ILTR’s assets, user information, including personal information collected from you through your use of the ILTR  Features, could be included in the transferred assets. Should such an event occur, we will use reasonable means to notify you through email and/or a prominent notice on the Site.

**Service Providers**

We may share your personal information with service providers that we engage for the purpose of processing information on our and your behalf. For example, we may partner with other companies to process payments for the ILTR  Features. Additionally, we may partner with other companies to process, analyze, and/or store data, including, but not limited to, Analytical Data. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. To the extent applicable, we require these entities to comply with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**4\. Additional Information You Should Know About Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of third party websites linked to the Site. Although we encourage such third parties to adopt and follow their own privacy policies, we are not responsible for their collection and use of your personal information. You should refer to the privacy policies and statements of other websites or contact the respective web-masters of those websites to obtain information regarding their information collection, use and disclosure policies.

When you have clicked on a third party logo or URL displayed on our Site which links you to a different website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the third party to see how your personal information will be handled on their website.

**5\. WHAT CHOICES DO YOU HAVE ABOUT THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

**Control of Your Information**

You may change or delete any information you’ve shared with use by sending us an email. We do keep records of past purchases and periodically back up information, so it may not be possible for you to delete all information we have stored, and we may retain certain information to prevent fraud and for customer and order management purposes.

**Opting Out of Receiving Communications from Us**

If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, emails or other announcements, you may unsubscribe by using the  unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails. 

**Mediation**

If you are a resident of a country outside of the European Union, you also agree that, in the event any dispute or claim arises out of or relating to this Privacy Policy that you and ILTR  will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the matter directly between the parties. You agree that if the matter remains unresolved for forty-five (45) days after notification (via certified mail or personal delivery) that a dispute exists, all parties shall join in mediation services in Los Angeles, California with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute. Should you file any arbitration claims, or any administrative or legal actions without first having attempted to resolve the matter by mediation, then you agree that you will not be entitled to recover attorneys’ fees, even if you would otherwise be entitled to them.

Dispute Resolution for Residents of the European Union

If you are a resident of the European Union, in the event that you have any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, you may report your claim to the European Union Data Protection Authorities located in your jurisdiction.

**6\. WHAT SECURITY MEASURES DO WE TAKE TO SAFEGUARD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

The personal information that you provide to us is stored on servers, which are located in secured facilities with restricted access, and protected by protocols and procedures designed to ensure the security of such information. In addition, we restrict access to personal information to ILTR  employees, independent contractors and agents who need to know this information in order to develop, operate and maintain the ILTR  Features. All ILTR  personnel who have access to this information are trained in the maintenance and security of such information. However, no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect user information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the use of any of the ILTR  Features and you acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. Once we receive a transmission from you, we will endeavor to maintain its security on our systems.

**7\. EUROPEAN COMMISSION’S DIRECTIVE ON DATA PROTECTION – SAFE HARBOR**

ILTR  adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles that were established by the U.S. Department of Commerce in consultation with the European Commission to comply with the European Commission **’** s Directive on Data Protection.

**8\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and we will post all changes on this page.

**9\. QUESTIONS? CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

**10\. TERMS OF USE**

Please read the [Terms of Use](http://www.ilovetoreview.com/terms-of-use/) governing the use of the Site and the ILTR  Features.
